<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>tracks</title>
    <link>https://maeniel.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on tracks</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 18:29:44 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://maeniel.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/post/goostuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2016 18:29:44 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/post/goostuff/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello world.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I think you&#39;re a contra, I think that you lie...</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2013/08/04/i-think-youre-a-contra-i-think-that-you-lie/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2013 12:46:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2013/08/04/i-think-youre-a-contra-i-think-that-you-lie/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;The inconvenient truth about the NSA is lying there on a table in the Ecuadorian Embassy, as stark as a poisoned crow. But it’ll join our planet’s many other inconvenient truths.

[- Bruce Sterling, Medium.com](https://medium.com/geek-empire-1/a1ebd2b4a0e5)

[![big_c5e3ef21f3229251a71a9b6c2c4b02a1fe9f96c0](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2013/08/big_c5e3ef21f3229251a71a9b6c2c4b02a1fe9f96c0-e1375620321753.png?w=460)](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2013/08/big_c5e3ef21f3229251a71a9b6c2c4b02a1fe9f96c0.png)&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My revolution thoughts, you little lies of desire
I wanna trace &amp;lsquo;em to the source and the wire
But it&amp;rsquo;s not useful now since we both made up our minds
You gonna watch out for yourself so will I&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=bRmNmoIPxWE&#34;&gt;I think ur a contra&amp;hellip;.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In this land of mistakes, I should lay my crosses down</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2013/06/12/in-this-land-of-mistakes-i-should-lay-my-crosses-down/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2013 01:40:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2013/06/12/in-this-land-of-mistakes-i-should-lay-my-crosses-down/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Jem was admitted to a hospital in Sydney, where the first step was an operation to find out what type of growth it was. Darling knew his daughter&amp;rsquo;s life hung in the balance. &amp;ldquo;The night before her surgery, I was kneeling beside her bed with my hand over the back of her head, close to the tumour,&amp;rdquo; he says. &amp;ldquo;I&amp;rsquo;m not a particularly religious person.&amp;rdquo; But on this occasion, he called on any help he could get. Five years later, he vividly recalls his desperation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.dungogchronicle.com.au/story/1558580/heart-and-mind/?cs=7&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;I was begging the universe to spare her.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VR3Dv74htec&#34;&gt;Dry The River&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>some people claim there&#39;s a woman to blame but i think i could my fault</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2012/07/07/some-people-claim-theres-a-women-to-blame-but-i-think-i-could-my-fault/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Jul 2012 14:21:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2012/07/07/some-people-claim-theres-a-women-to-blame-but-i-think-i-could-my-fault/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Tried google+ today. Then deleted it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2012/07/warning2.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2012/07/warning2.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>sunset run</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2012/04/14/dreamy-eyes-are-azure-blue/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2012 03:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2012/04/14/dreamy-eyes-are-azure-blue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2012/04/120400231.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2012/04/120400231.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[youtube &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DuhDOb0RMXA&amp;amp;w=853&amp;amp;h=480&#34;&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DuhDOb0RMXA&amp;amp;w=853&amp;amp;h=480&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>freedom</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2012/04/04/scenic-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Apr 2012 07:23:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2012/04/04/scenic-world/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://my.fsf.org/register_form?referrer=10295&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://static.fsf.org/nosvn/associate/fsf-10295.png&#34; alt=&#34;[FSF Associate Member]&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cause it&#39;s a beautiful night we&#39;re looking for something dumb to do</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2012/01/03/cause-its-a-beautiful-night-were-looking-for-something-dumb-to-do/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Jan 2012 11:31:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2012/01/03/cause-its-a-beautiful-night-were-looking-for-something-dumb-to-do/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;On the first day, God created the heavens and the earth.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Let there be light,” He said, and there was light. And God saw that it was good. And there was evening—the first night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the second day, God separated the oceans from the sky. “Let there be a horizon,” He said. And lo: a horizon appeared and God saw that it was good. And there was evening—the second night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the third day, God’s girlfriend came over and said that He’d been acting distant lately.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m sorry,” God said. “Things have been crazy this week at work.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He smiled at her, but she did not smile back. And God saw that it was not good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I never see you,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That’s not true,” God said. “We went to the movies just last week.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And she said, “Lo. That was last month.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And there was evening—a tense night.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the fourth day, God created stars, to divide the light from the darkness. He was almost finished when He looked at His cell phone and realized that it was almost nine-thirty.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Fuck,” He said. “Kate’s going to kill me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He finished the star He was working on and cabbed it back to the apartment.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Sorry I’m late!” He said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And lo: she did not even respond.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Are you hungry?” He asked. “Let there be yogurt!” And there was that weird lo-cal yogurt that she liked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That’s not going to work this time,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Look,” God said, “I know we’re going through a hard time right now. But this job is only temporary. As soon as I pay off my student loans, I’m going to switch to something with better hours.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And she said unto Him, “I work a full-time job and I still make time for you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And He said unto her, “Yeah, but your job’s different.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And lo: He knew immediately that He had made a terrible mistake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You think my job’s less important than yours?” she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“No!” God said. “Of course not! I know how difficult it is to work in retail—I’m totally impressed by what you do!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Today I had to talk to fourteen buyers, because it’s Fashion Week. And I didn’t even have time to eat lunch.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That’s so hard,” God said. “You work so hard.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“How would you know? You never even ask about my day! You just talk about your work, for hours and hours, like you’re the center of the universe!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Let there be a back rub,” God said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And He started giving her a back rub.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And she said unto Him, “Can you please take the day off tomorrow?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And He said unto her, “Don’t you have to work tomorrow? I thought it was Fashion Week.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I can call in sick.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And God felt like saying to her, “If your job is so important, how come you can just take days off whenever you feel like it?” But He knew that was a bad idea. So He said unto her, “I’m off Sunday. We can hang out Sunday.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the fifth day, God created fish and fowl to swim in the sea and fly through the air, each according to its kind. Then, to score some points, He closed the door to His office and called up Kate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I’m so happy to hear your voice,” she said. “I’m having the hardest day.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Tell me all about it,” God said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Caitlin is throwing this party next week for Jenny, but Jenny is, like, being so weird about it that I’m not even sure that it’s going to happen.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“That’s crazy,” God said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And she continued to tell Him about her friends, who had all said hurtful things to one another, each according to her kind. And while she was repeating something that Jenny had said to Caitlin God came up with an idea for creatures that roam the earth. He couldn’t get off the phone, though, because Kate was still talking. So He covered the receiver and whispered, “Let there be elephants.” And there were elephants and God saw that they were good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But lo: she had heard Him create the elephants.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Oh, my God,” she said. “You’re not even listening to me.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Kate &amp;hellip;”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“It’s so obvious!” she said. “You care more about your stupid planet thing than you do about me!”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;God wanted to correct her. It wasn’t just a planet He was creating; it was an entire universe. He knew, though, that it would be a bad idea to say something like that right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He said, “Listen. I’m really sorry, O.K.?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But lo: she had already hung up on Him.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the sixth day, God called in sick and surprised Kate at her store in Chelsea. She was in the back, reading a magazine.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What are you doing here?” she asked.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I blew off work,” He said. “I want to spend the day with you.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Really?” she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Really,” He said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And she smiled at Him so brightly that He knew He had made the right decision.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They bought some beers at a bodega and drank them on a bench in Prospect Park. And Kate introduced Him to a game her friend Jenny had taught her, called Would You Rather?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I don’t know if I want to play a game,” God said. But she made Him play anyway, and after a few rounds He saw that it was good. They played all afternoon, laughing at each other’s responses. When it got cold, God rubbed her shoulders and she kissed Him on the neck.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“You know what I kind of want to do right now?” Kate said. God tensed up.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“What?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“See a movie,” she said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And God laughed, because it was exactly what He wanted to do.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They decided to see “The Muppets,” because they had heard that it was good. They had a great time, and when it was over God paid for a cab so they wouldn’t have to wait all night for the L train.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I love you,” Kate said, as she nodded off in the back seat. “I love you so much.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“I love you, too,” God said.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And both of them saw that it was good.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On the seventh day, God quit His job. He never finished the earth. ♦
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.newyorker.com/humor/2012/01/09/120109sh_shouts_rich?currentPage=1&#34;&gt;-simon rich&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2012/01/381971_337810049580546_100000546627127_1272068_664617867_n_large.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2012/01/381971_337810049580546_100000546627127_1272068_664617867_n_large.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the devil puts a dollar into the valet&#39;s hands</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2011/03/21/populace/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2011 12:00:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2011/03/21/populace/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[](&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.abc.net.au/news/photos/2011/03/10/3159841.htm)[![](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2011/03/ztjpk.jpg)](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2011/03/ztjpk.jpg&#34;&gt;http://www.abc.net.au/news/photos/2011/03/10/3159841.htm)[![](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2011/03/ztjpk.jpg)](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2011/03/ztjpk.jpg&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The pin striped men of mornin&amp;rsquo;
Are comin&amp;rsquo; for to dance
With pure Egyptian cotton
The kids don&amp;rsquo;t stand a chance&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>remember it will all blow over, we&#39;ll meet again, when the temperature is lower</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2010/12/22/remember-well-meet-again-when-the-temperature-is-lower/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2010 23:09:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2010/12/22/remember-well-meet-again-when-the-temperature-is-lower/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For the celebrated naturalist Jean-Henri Fabre, when we make these value  judgments about insects it’s because we haven’t taken the trouble to  really know them. Of course, we can happily live our lives without doing  so, but how we would broaden our ideas if we did? Reading Jean-Henri  Fabre on flies is like reading Melville on the sea, or M.F.K. Fisher on  vegetables, blessed Sagan on the stars, or de Quincey on smack. Fabre’s  entomological writings are pure enthusiasm. He is legend among  naturalists of all stripes because he championed an idea that the rest  of us find nearly impossible to fathom: The more we pay attention to the  insects, the more we learn about the best and worst in ourselves. Read  Fabre and you will never look at a bug in the same way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the end of the chapter on bluebottle maggots, after the vivid  descriptions of slithering worms on rotting flesh, Fabre gets at what  is, perhaps, at the heart of our battle with the bugs. The bugs remind  us of our own limitations and our own mortality. In the course of life,  we can just barely control our proximity to the bugs. But when we die,  the instant we die, the bugs will finally get what they want most: to be  close to us. As you can imagine, Fabre finds a certain justice in this,  and from justice, comfort:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the surface of the soil, exposed to the air, the hideous  invasion is possible; ay, it is the invariable rule. For the melting  down and remolding of matter, man is no better, corpse for corpse, than  the lowest of the brutes. Then the fly exercises her rights and deals  with us as she does with any ordinary animal refuse. Nature treats us  with magnificent indifference in her great regenerating factory: placed  in her crucibles, animals and men, beggars and kings are one and all  alike. There you have true equality, the only equality in this world of  ours&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5rqITnk22RY&#34;&gt;The Treasure Stays Buried&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[](&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5rqITnk22RY&#34;&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=5rqITnk22RY&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cause if its ever gonna get any better its gotta get worse for a day</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2010/10/12/cause-if-its-ever-gonna-get-any-better-its-gotta-get-worse-for-a-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Oct 2010 00:17:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2010/10/12/cause-if-its-ever-gonna-get-any-better-its-gotta-get-worse-for-a-day/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.reddit.com/r/linux/&#34;&gt;reddit&lt;/a&gt; user : How Windows-user-friendly is the ports system these days? Does it have a  GUI to compete with the Ubuntu Add-Remove Software dialogue or Synaptic?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.perturb.org/display/Dilbert___Unix.html&#34;&gt;nix&lt;/a&gt; user : here is a nickel, go learn how to use the command line&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/10/6g4vq1.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/10/6g4vq1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>el burro</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2010/05/21/el-burro/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2010 01:14:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2010/05/21/el-burro/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;“Tell me, Maecenus,”&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.firstthings.com/article/2010/05/regard-the-scuttlebutt-as-true&#34;&gt; Juster&lt;/a&gt; has Horace ask his Roman patron and boss,
_ why no one’s content
with either what they’ve  done or fate has sent,
yet they applaud men taking other trails.
“O  lucky businessmen!” the soldier wails,
his body weighted down by  age and shattered.
Yet whenever southern winds have battered
his  boat, a businessman will surely cry,
“Can’t beat the army life!  Don’t you know why?
Two sides will clash, and in a flash you’ll see
a  sudden death or joyous victory.”_&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;_&lt;a href=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/05/fxxouu_large.png&#34;&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/05/fxxouu_large.png&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
_&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Words ought to be a little wild, for they are the assault of thoughts on the unthinking.</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2010/03/08/words-ought-to-be-a-little-wild-for-they-are-the-assault-of-thoughts-on-the-unthinking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 02:40:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2010/03/08/words-ought-to-be-a-little-wild-for-they-are-the-assault-of-thoughts-on-the-unthinking/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When the accumulation of wealth is no longer of high social importance, there will be great changes in the code of morals.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
We shall be able to rid ourselves of many of the pseudo-moral&lt;br /&gt;
principles which have hag-ridden us for two hundred years, by which we&lt;br /&gt;
have exalted some of the most distasteful of human qualities into the&lt;br /&gt;
position of the highest virtues. We shall be able to afford to dare to&lt;br /&gt;
assess the money-motive at its true value. &lt;strong&gt;The love of money as a&lt;br /&gt;
possession — as distinguished from the love of money as a means to the&lt;br /&gt;
enjoyments and realities of life — will be recognised for what it is, a&lt;br /&gt;
somewhat disgusting morbidity, one of those semi-criminal,&lt;br /&gt;
semi-pathological propensities which one hands over with a shudder to&lt;br /&gt;
the specialists in mental disease&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;hellip; &lt;strong&gt;But beware! The time for&lt;br /&gt;
all this is not yet. For at least another hundred years we must pretend&lt;br /&gt;
to ourselves and to everyone that fair is foul and foul is fair; for&lt;br /&gt;
foul is useful and fair is not. Avarice and usury and precaution must&lt;br /&gt;
be our gods for a little longer still.&lt;/strong&gt; For only they can lead us out of the tunnel of economic necessity into daylight.&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=d0nERTFo-Sk%20&#34;&gt;-Keynes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
&lt;img src=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/03/dsc01121.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.zemanta.com/pixy.gif?x-id=6a6f46a3-da00-88a7-bdd6-a3659cfbe512&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Content Found</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2010/02/26/450/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2010 01:34:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2010/02/26/450/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;At home I am a nice guy: but I  don&amp;rsquo;t want the world to know. Humble people, I&amp;rsquo;ve found, don&amp;rsquo;t get very  far. - Ali&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/02/tumblr_ky3l99jzzv1qzpwi0o1_500.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://img.zemanta.com/pixy.gif?x-id=ca0fa116-0369-81aa-b04c-538edffafbbd&#34; alt=&#34;&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>but for one crowded hour you were the only one in the room</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2010/02/13/but-for-one-crowded-hour-you-were-the-only-one-in-the-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Feb 2010 23:45:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2010/02/13/but-for-one-crowded-hour-you-were-the-only-one-in-the-room/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;[](&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qmwzq7QCW7Y)[![](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/02/stars_56.jpg)](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/02/stars_56.jpg&#34;&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qmwzq7QCW7Y)[![](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/02/stars_56.jpg)](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/02/stars_56.jpg&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qmwzq7QCW7Y&#34;&gt;There can be no happiness if the things we believe in are different from the things we do.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.archive.org/search.php?query=mediatype%3A(texts&#34;&gt;~Freya Stark,&lt;/a&gt; -contributor%3Agutenberg AND (subject%3A) The Journey’s Echo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qmwzq7QCW7Y&#34;&gt;http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Qmwzq7QCW7Y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>and i seem to find the happiness i seek when we&#39;re dancing cheek to cheek</title>
      <link>https://maeniel.com/2010/02/03/and-i-seem-to-find-the-happiness-i-seek-when-were-dancing-cheek-to-cheek/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2010 00:12:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://maeniel.com/2010/02/03/and-i-seem-to-find-the-happiness-i-seek-when-were-dancing-cheek-to-cheek/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;dumb-jokes-that-are-funny:0ce27ab7f52d555ade4cd2155fde23cc&#34;&gt;Dumb jokes that are funny.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-cannibal-went-for-a-walk-and-passed-his-brother:0ce27ab7f52d555ade4cd2155fde23cc&#34;&gt;A cannibal went for a walk and passed his brother.&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;[](&lt;a href=&#34;http://theoatmeal.com/djtaf/)[![](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/02/vader_with_a_parasol_med.jpg)](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/02/vader_with_a_parasol_med.jpg&#34;&gt;http://theoatmeal.com/djtaf/)[![](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/02/vader_with_a_parasol_med.jpg)](https://maeniel.files.wordpress.com/2010/02/vader_with_a_parasol_med.jpg&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>